Register of the Abortion Litigation Papers of Roy Lucas, 1967 - 1973
Abortion Litigation Papers of Roy Lucas, 1967 - 1973
- Research
  - Judicial Notice (Box 27)
  - Referral Services: Practical Medicine (Box 27)
  - Ninth Amendment -- Constitutional Privacy (Box 27)
  - Abortion: U.S. Common Law cases (Box 27)
  - Status of Foetus: Commentary (Box 27)
  - Foetus: Property Rights (Box 27)
  - Foetus Tort Cases (Box 27)
    - Pre-Natal Injuries - No Recovery (Box 27)
    - Pre-Natal Injuries - Recovery if Viable (Box 27)
    - Pre-Natal Injuries - Recovery, Not Viable (Box 27)
  - Foetus: (Box 27)
    - Wrong Death -No Recovery at all (Box 27)
    - Wrong Death -Recovery if Viable (Box 27)
    - Wrong Death -Recovery, Not Viable (Box 27)
- Publications
  Copies of articles about abortion and abortion laws, including newspaper clippings about court cases, arranged chronologically.
  - Roy Lucas (Box 28)
    - "Federal Constitutional Limitations on Enforcement and Administration" (Box 28)
    - "Abortion Laws in the U.S. " (Box 28)
    - "The Abortion Revolution" (2 copies) (Box 28)
    - "The Right to Higher Education" (7 copies) (Box 28)
    - "Student Rights and Responsibilities" (Box 28)
  - Abortion Clippings, 1967-1973, undated (Box 28)
  - Miscellaneous Publications (Box 28)